uspoloassn.com 2017-07-22

# Privacy Policy - U.S. Polo Assn.

Welcome to USPoloAssn.com (the "Site").  The U.S. Polo Assn. USA, a division of JRA Trademark LTD, ("Company", "we", "us" or "our"), provides the Site, and the services on the Site, subject to the following terms and conditions (the "Terms of Use"). These Terms of Use set forth the terms governing your use of the Site. In addition, when you use any service on the Site you will also be subject to the rules, policies, terms and conditions applicable to such service. These rules, policies, terms and conditions are incorporated herein by reference.   

This Policy describes our privacy practices and establishes obligations and expectations in respect to your use of the Site. We want you to be aware of the information we collect, how we use it and with whom we share it. This Policy applies only to the Site and does not necessarily apply to our off-line collection of information. By visiting the Site, you agree to the terms of this Policy and the terms of use (the "Terms of Use").

We reserve the right to revise or make changes to this Policy at any time. We will communicate any such changes on this page. The date of the latest Policy revision can be found on the bottom of this page. You may bookmark this page and review it periodically to ensure familiarity with the most current version of this Policy. Your continual use of the Site subsequent to any changes to this Policy will mean that you accept such changes. At any point should you wish to remove any portion of your personal information from our database, please notify us at [serviceUSA@e.uspoloassn.com](mailto:serviceUSA@e.uspoloassn.com).

BY VISITING THE SITE YOU CONSENT TO OUR USE OF ANY INFORMATION PROVIDED TO US OR THAT WE COLLECT, IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE, DO NOT VISIT OR USE THE SITE.

 **Information We Collect and Track**

The Company collects and retains two types of information from Site visitors: (i) personal information voluntarily provided by individual visitors when interacting on the Site, or on certain other occasions, such as via forms or in emails; and (ii) tracking data, which is automatically collected from every Site visitor and recorded on our log files, (collectively, "Information"). The Information that we gather may include your name, title and address, telephone number, email address, birth date and credit card number, as well as other elements of personal information. In addition, we may keep a record of any correspondence, including any Information contained therein. We may collect this information when you:

  * Place an order on the Site.  

  * Return an item or make an exchange.  

  * Inquire about our services.  

  * Create an account on the Site.  

  * Sign up for email updates from the Company.  

  * Are referred to us through a marketing promotion.  

  * Participate in a Company marketing survey, promotion, or event.  

You may decline to provide any personal information, but this may prohibit registration on the Site or limit participation in activities or services offered on the Site.

In an effort to improve our site we may collect non-personal information about how users navigate through the Site. Without limitation, we may collect information regarding the number and frequency of visits to the Site, viewed and/or purchased items, information on websites accessed prior to and following your visit to the Site, the software used to access the Site, your IP address and Internet service provider-related information. The tracking data we record may include the location of your computer.

 **How We Use Your Information**

The Information that we collect is used for a variety of business purposes, including but not limited to, retaining transaction and order information, processing and tracking orders, contacting you about the status of an order, providing information regarding product recalls or products you have purchased, responding to your requests or correspondence and to find ways in which we can improve the Site. We may also use your Information to advise you of upcoming activities, promotions, products, services and events in which we think you may be interested. Your Information may be analyzed to enable us to serve you in the best manner possible through enhanced features and functions on the Site.

We will not disclose any personal information to third parties, except (i) to parties who perform a service for us, such as email service providers, web hosting, credit card processing, shipping services, and other similar services; (ii) when we believe that such disclosure is required by law; (iii) to enforce this Policy or the Terms of Use; (iv) to protect the rights, property, security or safety of the Company, Site users or the public; (v) to respond to an emergency; or (vi) as otherwise stated in this Policy. In addition, we may disclose Information to certain third parties upon your request or authorization.

We provide certain Information to third party service providers who perform specific functions on our behalf. Certain service providers (i.e., web hosting, credit card processing, shipping, order tracking, catalog management and others) may have access to all, or part, of the Information we maintain. All such Information provided to third parties is limited to the Information needed to perform their functions. We seek to limit third-party use of Information; however, we are not responsible for such third-party use of Information that is not in compliance with this Policy.

The Company may make certain Information, including, but not limited to, your name, address and email address available to our affiliates and related companies. This information is never sold. Our affiliates and related companies may contact you directly regarding certain promotions. If you would like to opt out of having the Company share your name, address, and email address with its affiliates and related companies, please contact our Customer Service Department.

The Company may collect certain tracking data that can be used for a variety of purposes including, but not limited to, analysis, load balancing metrics and creating reports on statistical, demographic or aggregated information about visitors to the Site. Reports generated from tracking data are used for a variety of purposes including improvements to the Site and our services.

 **Use of Cookies**

We use cookies to enhance your experience while using the Site. "Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies facilitate web browsing by performing certain functions, such as saving passwords and personal preferences, in connection with your use of a particular website. Your browser is most likely set to accept cookies, but you are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. If you choose to set your browser to prohibit cookies, it is possible that some of the Services provided on the Site will not function properly. We may also contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We prohibit these companies from using this information on their own behalf or from sharing this information with anyone other than the Company.

Transfer of Information to Third Parties upon Sale or Change of Control

We retain the right to transfer or assign all Information pursuant to a merger, sale, reorganization, purchase or other transaction relating to the Company, its affiliates or their assets, if the assignee or purchaser agrees to abide by the terms of this Policy.

 **Information Protection**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your Information from loss, misuse or alteration. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your non-public Information. You should recognize, however, that there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet and we cannot guarantee the security of your Information. Due to the unsecure nature of Internet communication, it is possible that information provided to us or information accessed via your use of the Site will be intercepted during transmission. We are not liable for any breach of our systems or interception of our transmission, and we hereby disclaim, to the fullest extent provided under law, any liability associated with any claim relating to a breach of security, data or information.

 **Other Communications**

From time to time, we may communicate marketing events, Site updates and changes or other developments at the Company to Site users via email. Such emails may be sent to users of the Site even if they have not requested to receive any communication from us. If you wish to unsubscribe from such email communication, please click here to unsubscribe.

 **Referrals**

If a user elects to use our referral service to inform another person about the Site or Site features, we may request the name and email address of such other person. The Company will automatically send a one-time email inviting such other person to visit the Site or to purchase items from the Company. The Company stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

 **Links to Third-Party Sites**

The Site may contain links to websites owned and operated by other parties. We are not responsible for, and have no control over the privacy policies of those sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those sites prior to providing them with any information.

 **Children's Privacy**

The Company is concerned with protecting the privacy of children who access the Internet and, thus, comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). Accordingly, the Site is not intended for use by anyone under the age of 13 without the supervision of a parent or guardian. We do not knowingly collect Information from anyone under 13 years of age without the consent of a parent or guardian. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any personal information to us, you may rely on your parent or guardian to assist you.

 **Law Compliance**

We reserve the right to disclose any Information to maintain compliance with any law, regulation, decree, judgment, order, subpoena or any other governmental order ("Order"), without any obligation to contest or verify the accuracy of such Order.

 **Applicable Law**

This Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree that any action at law or in equity that arises out of, or relates to any use of the Site will be filed only in the state or federal courts located in the State of New York, and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action.

 **Updating or Correct Your Information and Contacting the Site**

Please contact our Customer Service Department if you have any questions or concerns regarding the Site, this Policy or if you would like to update or correct your Information. Please send any questions or comments regarding this Site to:

U. S. Polo Assn. USA Ecommerce

1400 Broadway, 15th Floor

New York, NY 10018

Our policy was last updated on January 31, 2017.
